still work
[music]
apartment is not rented out
and here is a cool clean new thing
that the function is a quiet knife and
So
we supply resources
[music]
required
Good work of all people for rent on
communication [
music]
thousands
[applause]
robots
[music]
[music] [music] [music
]
[music]
we will need us
and
furiously 9 stretch so cool almost fierce
work I saw a mortar in black On the
beautiful in vain just
on the third day
[music]
almost makadilis
being here and close arthritic
So you're joking Let him
want
[music] [
music]
I saw Pobachev was honest Red snake according to
But Christie
I said so swear
[music]
and you can earn for
the guard and my everyday life on miners
good karma and lips here forgot 10
Rocky in that  I
was torn between classes today,
Yakub's karma solution, this is
wonderful, it can
[music]
You can
all these
choices,
guys, you can do
them with creation, a
machine, many cars,
explosions, intuition, love
and an hour, then like
in the unit,
and
so simply, you are such a John
[music]
simple until the morning
friends, too, good so that he knows more mana,
floor, boss,
another quote
[music]
it's
called the mantra of the name, I
and I from the crack, he is different, ancient traditions were carried out
I want to mutter a mantra
[music]
one mantra 12 Centuries,
my you can dissolve still here, it's
nice
[music]
maybe and say more I take away the suffering of
all living creatures I give
[music]
task
I will be Friday, I will be a bit cramped for you in front of
your boss,
good, try
all my great mantra for your
practice,
you can
[music] [
music]
[music]